# samuel asamoah

## Summary

Self-taught graphic designer and programmer who has recently graduated high-school. Committed to learning, creating, and utilizing my skills in the service of others in need. Experienced at developing innovative ideas through design and materializing these ideas through code.

#### Education

## International School of Kenya

High-School Diploma • Niarobi

05/2020

#### **Course Selection:**

- IB Economics Higher Level
- IB Physics Higher Level
- IB Design Technology Higher Level
- IB Mathematics Standard Level
- IB English Standard Level
- IB Swahili Ab Initio IB Theory of Knowledge

## **Awards**

- High Hounor Roll (2019, 2018)
- Hounor Roll (2017)

## **Experience**

## **Safaricom**

Intern • Nairobi 09/2018 - 10/2018

Aided in the development of a phone application which allows a user to manage assets digitally.

## **Bongo University**

Designer • Virginia 05/2018 - 07/2018

Designed African inspired t-shirt graphics which were sold online.

## **Fiverr**

Freelance Graphic Designer

06/2017 - 07/2017

Cooperated with Fiverr clients found around the world to design t-shirts, logos, posters, and websites.

#### Skills

- · Web Development
- · iOS Development
- Graphic Design

· Amazon AWS Cloud Practitioner

## **Link to Portfolio**

https://www.behance.net/aleumas250e6a